var quizArray = [{
		"id":"0",
		"question":"Size of mapping playable in GTA: San Andreas",
		"choice1":"44 sq miles",
		"choice2":"45 sq miles",
		"choice3":"46 sq miles",
		"choice4":"47 sq miles",
		"correct":"44 sq miles"
	},
	{
	"id":"1",
		"question":"Maximum possible score in Pac-Man.",
		"choice1":"3,222,360 points",
		"choice2":"3,333,360 points",
		"choice3":"3,555,360 points",
		"choice4":"3,444,360 points",
		"correct":"3,333,360 points"
	},
	{
	"id":"2",
		"question":"What was the first product marketed by Sony?",
		"choice1":"TV",
		"choice2":"Kettle of Rice",
		"choice3":"Rice Cooker",
		"choice4":"Radio",
		"correct":"Kettle of Rice"
	},
	{
	"id":"3",
		"question":"How many ways of training is available in Armored Core Nine Breaker?",
		"choice1":"100",
		"choice2":"150",
		"choice3":"200",
		"choice4":"250",
		"correct":"150"
	},
	{
	"id":"4",
		"question":"In the original Donkey Kong game, Mario is called what?",
		"choice1":"Plumber",
		"choice2":"Carpenter",
		"choice3":"Jumpman",
		"choice4":"Mushroom Man",
		"correct":"Jumpman"
	},
	{
	"id":"5",
		"question":"How many equipments are there in Final Fantasy X?",
		"choice1":"501",
		"choice2":"502",
		"choice3":"503",
		"choice4":"504",
		"correct":"504"
	},
	{
	"id":"6",
		"question":"Michael Jackson appeared on every video game below EXCEPT one.",
		"choice1":"Sonic the Hedgehog 3",
		"choice2":"Ready 2 Rumble 2",
		"choice3":"Moon Walker",
		"choice4":"Resident Evil 4",
		"correct":"Resident Evil 4"
	},
	{
	"id":"7",
		"question":"What does the Fable: The Lost Chapters contains?",
		"choice1":"Fairies",
		"choice2":"Relic",
		"choice3":"Tomb of Peter Molyneux",
		"choice4":"Treasure",
		"correct":"Tomb of Peter Molyneux"
	},
	{
	"id":"8",
		"question":"What is the original developer of Red Dead Revolver?",
		"choice1":"Sony",
		"choice2":"Square Enix",
		"choice3":"Capcom",
		"choice4":"Rockstar",
		"correct":"Capcom"
	},
	{
	"id":"9",
		"question":"What is the best selling Xbox game?",
		"choice1":"Halo",
		"choice2":"Halo2",
		"choice3":"COD: Modern Warfare",
		"choice4":"COD: Black Ops",
		"correct":"Halo2"
	},
	{
	"id":"10",
		"question":"ICO is a derivation of the Japanese word, what is it ?",
		"choice1":"Let's Go",
		"choice2":"Go Away",
		"choice3":"Hello",
		"choice4":"Bye",
		"correct":"Let's Go"
	},
	{
	"id":"11",
		"question":"The president of Nintendo of America, Reggie Fils-Aime was a formerly director of national marketing master of what Company?",
		"choice1":"Greenwich",
		"choice2":"Pizza Hut",
		"choice3":"Yellow Cab",
		"choice4":"Jollibee",
		"correct":"Pizza Hut"
	},
	{
	"id":"12",
		"question":"In the game Tomb Raider, Lara Croft, is originally named as?",
		"choice1":"Laura Croft",
		"choice2":"Lara Cruz",
		"choice3":"Laura Cruz",
		"choice4":"Sara Croft",
		"correct":"Laura Cruz"
	},
	{
	"id":"13",
		"question":"What is the suggested name for the game Nintendo Mario, also known as Mario Bros?",
		"choice1":"MARIO",
		"choice2":"Mario Brothers",
		"choice3":"Mario the Jumpman",
		"choice4":"Plumber Mario",
		"correct":"MARIO"
	},
	{
	"id":"14",
		"question":"The first game of Dynasty Warriors, was a? ",
		"choice1":"First Person Shooting",
		"choice2":"Tower Defence",
		"choice3":"Beat em up face to face",
		"choice4":"RPG",
		"correct":"Beat em up face to face"
	},
	
	{
	"id":"15",
		"question":"Gran Turismo 2 had close to how many cars? ",
		"choice1":"630",
		"choice2":"640",
		"choice3":"650",
		"choice4":"660",
		"correct":"650"
	},

	{
	"id":"16",
		"question":"Gran Turismo 2 had close to 650 cars, how about Gran Turismo 3? ",
		"choice1":"Yes",
		"choice2":"No",
		"choice3":"Maybe",
		"choice4":"Absolutely",
		"correct":"No"
	},
	{
	"id":"17",
		"question":"Who is the Nintendo president who owns a majority stake of the baseball team Seattle Marines? ",
		"choice1":"Hiroshi Yamauchi",
		"choice2":"Hiro Yamaguchi",
		"choice3":"Hiroshi Yamaguchi",
		"choice4":"Roshi Yamauchi",
		"correct":"Hiroshi Yamauchi"
	},
	{
	"id":"18",
		"question":"Who is the Director of Katamari Games? ",
		"choice1":"Hiroshi Yamauchi",
		"choice2":"Keita Takahashi",
		"choice3":"Keita Takashi",
		"choice4":"Roshi Yamauchi",
		"correct":"Keita Takahashi"
	},
	{
	"id":"19",
		"question":"What is the plan in the Early Development of Final Fantasy XII? ",
		"choice1":"Allows a Second Player to the Party",
		"choice2":"Allows Hero/Heroine Customizing",
		"choice3":"Allows Skipping Missions",
		"choice4":"Allows Changing Main Character",
		"correct":"Allows a Second Player to the Party"
	},
	{
	"id":"20",
		"question":"In the year 2001, a pair of students created a version of pong, giving lashes, burns, or electrical shock to the loser. What is it called?",
		"choice1":"No Pain No Game",
		"choice2":"Torture Pong",
		"choice3":"PainStation",
		"choice4":"PainGame",
		"correct":"PainStation"
	},
	{
	"id":"21",
		"question":"Who is the Voice actor of Solid Snake in Metal Gear Solid games? ",
		"choice1":"David Blaine",
		"choice2":"David Hade",
		"choice3":"David Hayter",
		"choice4":"David Hanes",
		"correct":"David Hayter"
	},
	{
	"id":"22",
		"question":"Who is the writer of the screenplay for X-Men? ",
		"choice1":"David Blaine",
		"choice2":"David Hade",
		"choice3":"David Hayter",
		"choice4":"David Hanes",
		"correct":"David Hayter"
	},
	{
	"id":"23",
		"question":"Nearly half the Disk space of Elder Scrolls IV: Oblivion are? ",
		"choice1":"Dialogues",
		"choice2":"Items",
		"choice3":"Cut scenes",
		"choice4":"Scenes",
		"correct":"Dialogues"
	},
	{
	"id":"24",
		"question":"The First GTA was released on what date? ",
		"choice1":"E3 '94",
		"choice2":"E3 '95",
		"choice3":"E3 '96",
		"choice4":"E3 '97",
		"correct":"E3 '97"
	},
	{
	"id":"25",
		"question":"On the first GTA, the audience were told that it would take about how many minutes to drive from one end of the city's game to another?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"3",
		"choice3":"2",
		"choice4":"1",
		"correct":"3"
	},
	{
	"id":"26",
		"question":"What will you find in the roof at the level of the single player campaign,Metropolis, of Halo 2?",
		"choice1":"Giant Football",
		"choice2":"Giant Basketball",
		"choice3":"Giant Baseball",
		"choice4":"Giant Volleyball",
		"correct":"Giant Football"
	},
	{
	"id":"27",
		"question":"The title 'Pikmin' dog is in honor of whom?",
		"choice1":"Hiyori Miyamoto",
		"choice2":"Rein Miyamoto",
		"choice3":"Shigeru Miyamoto",
		"choice4":"Yuuki Miyamoto",
		"correct":"Shigeru Miyamoto"
	},
	{
	"id":"28",
		"question":"The 'Outrun' of Sega, has appeared in how many formats?",
		"choice1":"18",
		"choice2":"19",
		"choice3":"20",
		"choice4":"21",
		"correct":"19"
	},
	{
	"id":"29",
		"question":"A game of Animal Crossing for Gamecube, can potentially last up to how many years?",
		"choice1":"28",
		"choice2":"29",
		"choice3":"30",
		"choice4":"31",
		"correct":"29"
	},
	{
	"id":"30",
		"question":"What is the most powerful weapon in the game of American McGee’s Bad Day LA?",
		"choice1":"The Chainsaw",
		"choice2":"The Gun",
		"choice3":"The Knife",
		"choice4":"The Clippers",
		"correct":"The Clippers"
	},
	{
	"id":"31",
		"question":"Who is the man who gave voice to the head teacher? a DJ for a station of radio in Chicago.",
		"choice1":"Steve Sun",
		"choice2":"Steve Kerr",
		"choice3":"Steve Joe",
		"choice4":"Steve Downes",
		"correct":"Steve Downes"
	},
	{
	"id":"32",
		"question":"What is the name of the clone of the game Space Invaders?",
		"choice1":"Space Infiltrators",
		"choice2":"Communist Mutants from Space",
		"choice3":"Mutants from Space",
		"choice4":"Space Mutants",
		"correct":"Communist Mutants from Space"
	},
	{
	"id":"33",
		"question":"Who is one of the Guru-Programmers of the game 'Doom'?",
		"choice1":"John Gale",
		"choice2":"John Galt",
		"choice3":"John Cormack",
		"choice4":"John Corsack",
		"correct":"John Cormack"
	},
	{
	"id":"34",
		"question":"Who is one of the Guru-Programmers of the game 'Doom', that also an employee volunteer Armadillo Aerospace?",
		"choice1":"John Gale",
		"choice2":"John Galt",
		"choice3":"John Cormack",
		"choice4":"John Corsack",
		"correct":"John Cormack"
	},
	{
	"id":"35",
		"question":"What is the team responsible for the portage of Resident Evil 2 to N64?",
		"choice1":"Rockstar San Diego",
		"choice2":"Capcom",
		"choice3":"Square Enix",
		"choice4":"Sony",
		"correct":"Rockstar San Diego"
	},
	{
	"id":"36",
		"question":"'Nintendo' is translated as?",
		"choice1":"Heaven's Luck",
		"choice2":"Leave Luck to Heaven",
		"choice3":"Luck Leaved to Heaven",
		"choice4":"Heavenly Luck",
		"correct":"Leave Luck to Heaven"
	},
	{
	"id":"37",
		"question":"'It is so called because of the creator and co-founder of Square, Hironobu Sakaguchi, using the Last Reserves of the Money from the company to do so.",
		"choice1":"Final Fantasy",
		"choice2":"Final Haven",
		"choice3":"Final Resolve",
		"choice4":"Final Destination",
		"correct":"Final Fantasy"
	},
	{
	"id":"38",
		"question":"'How many parts of Final Fantasy(sub parts not included) are present up to now?",
		"choice1":"12",
		"choice2":"13",
		"choice3":"14",
		"choice4":"15",
		"correct":"15"
	},
	{
	"id":"39",
		"question":"'What is the Owner Company of Final Fantasy?",
		"choice1":"Square Enix/Square",
		"choice2":"Sony",
		"choice3":"Nintendo",
		"choice4":"Xbox",
		"correct":"Square Enix/Square"
	},
	{
	"id":"40",
		"question":"'Who is the owner / co-founder of Square / Square Enix?",
		"choice1":"Hiro Sakachi",
		"choice2":"Hirobu Sakabuci",
		"choice3":"Hironobu Sakaguchi",
		"choice4":"Hiromi Sakashi",
		"correct":"Hironobu Sakaguchi"
	},
	{
	"id":"41",
		"question":"'Who is Terry Butcher?",
		"choice1":"NBA Player",
		"choice2":"Manager of Brentford FC",
		"choice3":"Soccer Player",
		"choice4":"Game Developer",
		"correct":"Manager of Brentford FC"
	},
	{
	"id":"42",
		"question":"'Who made the opening remarks of Pro Evolution Soccer 2001?",
		"choice1":"Terry Jones",
		"choice2":"Jason Terry",
		"choice3":"Terry Butcher",
		"choice4":"Terry Swan",
		"correct":"Terry Butcher"
	},
	{
	"id":"43",
		"question":"'In late 2005, what contract did Sony signed to promote PSP?",
		"choice1":"To Graffiti 7 Cities in USA",
		"choice2":"To Promote Large Billboards in 7 Cities of USA",
		"choice3":"Create a Huge mass of Convention for 7 days",
		"choice4":"Created a Commercial",
		"correct":"To Graffiti 7 Cities in USA"
	},
	{
	"id":"44",
		"question":"'CAPCOM is the abbreviation of?",
		"choice1":"Capsule Communication",
		"choice2":"Capsule Computers",
		"choice3":"Capsule Command",
		"choice4":"Capsule Commercial",
		"correct":"Capsule Computers"
	},
	{
	"id":"45",
		"question":"'Does Yoshi have teeth?",
		"choice1":"Probably??",
		"choice2":"Maybe?...",
		"choice3":"No??",
		"choice4":"In spite of that, Yes",
		"correct":"In spite of that, Yes"
	},
	{
	"id":"46",
		"question":"'In UK, what is the best selling game of PSX the whole time?",
		"choice1":"Final Fantasy 7",
		"choice2":"Crash Bandicoot",
		"choice3":"Rayman",
		"choice4":"Resident Evil: Nemesis",
		"correct":"Rayman"
	},
	{
	"id":"47",
		"question":"'Why is Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory banned it South Korea?",
		"choice1":"Because it's too violent",
		"choice2":"Because it contains destruction of Seoul, Korea",
		"choice3":"Because it defies some Korean Law",
		"choice4":"Because it contains negative Statement about South Korea",
		"correct":"Because it contains destruction of Seoul, Korea"
	},
	{
	"id":"48",
		"question":"'Splinter Cell: Chaos Theory was banned it South Korea. What year was it Lifted?",
		"choice1":"2009",
		"choice2":"2008",
		"choice3":"2007",
		"choice4":"2006",
		"correct":"2006"
	},
	{
	"id":"49",
		"question":"'What Resident Evil game is the only non-spinoff?",
		"choice1":"Resident Evil 2",
		"choice2":"Resident Evil Zero",
		"choice3":"Resident Evil : Director's Cut",
		"choice4":"Resident Evil : Biohazard",
		"correct":"Resident Evil Zero"
	},
	{
	"id":"50",
		"question":"'Resident Evil Zero is only Exclusive of what format?",
		"choice1":"PSX",
		"choice2":"PS 2",
		"choice3":"Game Cube",
		"choice4":"PSP",
		"correct":"Game Cube"
	},
	{
	"id":"51",
		"question":"'Psychonauts managed to sell less 90,000 of copies to PS2, Xbox and what?",
		"choice1":"Game Cube",
		"choice2":"Nintendo Wii",
		"choice3":"PSP",
		"choice4":"PC",
		"correct":"PC"
	},
	{
	"id":"52",
		"question":"'From what movie came the names of all the pigeons in Killer 7?",
		"choice1":"Female Characters from James Bond",
		"choice2":"Rangers from Power Rangers",
		"choice3":"Any Random Names",
		"choice4":"Any Characters from Bourne Series",
		"correct":"Female Characters from James Bond"
	},
	{
	"id":"53",
		"question":"'Saints Row for Xbox 360 contains most of how many licensed tracks?",
		"choice1":"110",
		"choice2":"120",
		"choice3":"130",
		"choice4":"140",
		"correct":"130"
	},
	{
	"id":"54",
		"question":"Saints Row for Xbox 360 contains most of 130 licensed tracks, how many of them are classical music?",
		"choice1":"40",
		"choice2":"45",
		"choice3":"50",
		"choice4":"55",
		"correct":"40"
	},
	{
	"id":"55",
		"question":"What game is prohibited in New Zealand, and having a copy of it is a Crime?",
		"choice1":"Manhunt",
		"choice2":"Splinter Cell",
		"choice3":"Ashpalt",
		"choice4":"Gran Turismo",
		"correct":"Manhunt"
	},
	{
	"id":"56",
		"question":"Manhunt is banned in a certain country, and having a copy of it is a Crime. What is this country?",
		"choice1":"New Zealand",
		"choice2":"Netherlands",
		"choice3":"Russia",
		"choice4":"France",
		"correct":"New Zealand"
	},
	{
	"id":"57",
		"question":"At E3 2004, how many games are showed?",
		"choice1":"5,000",
		"choice2":"6,000",
		"choice3":"7,000",
		"choice4":"8,000",
		"correct":"5,000"
	},
	{
	"id":"58",
		"question":"At E3 2004, nearly 5,000 games are showed. How many of those were entirely new?",
		"choice1":"1,000",
		"choice2":"2,000",
		"choice3":"3,000",
		"choice4":"4,000",
		"correct":"1,000"
	},
	{
	"id":"59",
		"question":"At E3 2004, showed nearly 5000 games. 1000 of those which were entirely new, at least how many are classified as educational games?",
		"choice1":"13percent",
		"choice2":"14percent",
		"choice3":"15percent",
		"choice4":"16percent",
		"correct":"16percent"
	},
	{
	"id":"60",
		"question":"How many cars are there in Gran Turismo 4?",
		"choice1":"550",
		"choice2":"650",
		"choice3":"700",
		"choice4":"750",
		"correct":"700"
	},
	{
	"id":"61",
		"question":"Each one of the most 700 cars in Gran Turismo 4, costs how many month for the designers to create?",
		"choice1":"half a month",
		"choice2":"one month",
		"choice3":"two months",
		"choice4":"three months",
		"correct":"one month"
	},
	{
	"id":"62",
		"question":"How many destructible object on each circuit are there in Flatout 2?",
		"choice1":"4,500",
		"choice2":"5,000",
		"choice3":"5,500",
		"choice4":"6,000",
		"correct":"5,000"
	},
	{
	"id":"63",
		"question":"How many CDs did it take for the soundtrack of Okami?",
		"choice1":"5 cds",
		"choice2":"6 cds",
		"choice3":"7 cds",
		"choice4":"8 cds",
		"correct":"5 cds"
	},
	{
	"id":"64",
		"question":"What is the Xbox original call name?",
		"choice1":"DirectX-box",
		"choice2":"X Boxing",
		"choice3":"Box X",
		"choice4":"DeX Box",
		"correct":"DirectX-box"
	},
	{
	"id":"65",
		"question":"Beside Nintendo, what other business did director Hiroshi Yamauchi had?",
		"choice1":"Television Channel",
		"choice2":"Taxi Firm",
		"choice3":"Music Company",
		"choice4":"Dance Studio",
		"correct":"Taxi Firm"
	},
	{
	"id":"66",
		"question":"Beside Nintendo and a Taxi Firm, what other business did director Hiroshi Yamauchi had?",
		"choice1":"Television Channel",
		"choice2":"Love Hotel",
		"choice3":"Music Company",
		"choice4":"Dance Studio",
		"correct":"Love Hotel"
	},
	{
	"id":"67",
		"question":"What is the best selling game on Gamecube?",
		"choice1":"Resident Evil Zero",
		"choice2":"Mario Cart Dash",
		"choice3":"Super Mario Bros.",
		"choice4":"Super Mario Bros. Melee",
		"correct":"Super Mario Bros. Melee"
	},
	{
	"id":"68",
		"question":"How long did The Sims stayed in the top ten of PC of UK sales?",
		"choice1":"85 weeks",
		"choice2":"84 weeks",
		"choice3":"83 weeks",
		"choice4":"82 weeks",
		"correct":"82 weeks"
	},
	{
	"id":"69",
		"question":"In the game 'Max Payne' who wrote the script and storyline?",
		"choice1":"Sam Lake",
		"choice2":"Sam Witwicky",
		"choice3":"Sam Jones",
		"choice4":"Sam Jackson",
		"correct":"Sam Lake"
	},
	{
	"id":"70",
		"question":"The face of Max Payne is modelled after the face of who?",
		"choice1":"Sam Lake",
		"choice2":"Sam Witwicky",
		"choice3":"Sam Jones",
		"choice4":"Sam Jackson",
		"correct":"Sam Lake"
	},
	{
	"id":"71",
		"question":"What is the meaning of 'DotA'?",
		"choice1":"Defence of the Ancients",
		"choice2":"Dirge and the Armours",
		"choice3":"Destroy all the Ancient",
		"choice4":"Destroy all the Armours",
		"correct":"Defence of the Ancients"
	},
	{
	"id":"72",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA' who is the Priestess of the Moon?",
		"choice1":"Mirana Nightshade",
		"choice2":"Luna Moonfang",
		"choice3":"Naga Siren",
		"choice4":"Lina Inverse",
		"correct":"Mirana Nightshade"
	},
	{
	"id":"73",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA' what will Roshan dropped if you killed it?",
		"choice1":"Assault Cuirass",
		"choice2":"Aegis of Immortal",
		"choice3":"Divine Rapier",
		"choice4":"Radiance",
		"correct":"Aegis of Immortal"
	},
	{
	"id":"74",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA' what item will be dropped if the carrier dies?",
		"choice1":"Assault Cuirass",
		"choice2":"Aegis of Immortal",
		"choice3":"Divine Rapier",
		"choice4":"Radiance",
		"correct":"Divine Rapier"
	},
	{
	"id":"75",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA' what is the total cost of Divine Rapier?",
		"choice1":"6,000 gold",
		"choice2":"6,100 gold",
		"choice3":"6,200 gold",
		"choice4":"6,300 gold",
		"correct":"6,200 gold"
	},
	{
	"id":"76",
		"question":"All heroes' ultimate can be upgraded by Aghanims Scepter, EXCEPT for one.",
		"choice1":"Lina Inverse",
		"choice2":"Lion",
		"choice3":"Traxex",
		"choice4":"Bane Elemental",
		"correct":"Traxex"
	},
	{
	"id":"77",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Kunkka cannot carry the item?",
		"choice1":"Kelen's Dagger of Escape",
		"choice2":"Quelling Blade",
		"choice3":"Radiance",
		"choice4":"Battle Fury",
		"correct":"Quelling Blade"
	},
	{
	"id":"78",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the name of Yurnero's Ultimate Skill?",
		"choice1":"Coup de Grace",
		"choice2":"Omnislash",
		"choice3":"Finger of Death",
		"choice4":"Critical Slash",
		"correct":"Omnislash"
	},
	{
	"id":"79",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Who among the heroes has the most number of skill?",
		"choice1":"Shadow Fiend",
		"choice2":"Morphling",
		"choice3":"Invoker",
		"choice4":"Chen",
		"correct":"Invoker"
	},
	{
	"id":"80",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What skill combination will allow the Invoker to use Meteor?",
		"choice1":"EEW",
		"choice2":"QQW",
		"choice3":"WWQ",
		"choice4":"QWE",
		"correct":"EEW"
	},
	{
	"id":"81",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What skill combination will allow the Invoker to use Tornado?",
		"choice1":"EEW",
		"choice2":"QQW",
		"choice3":"WWQ",
		"choice4":"QWE",
		"correct":"WWQ"
	},
	{
	"id":"82",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What skill combination will allow the Invoker to use Sun Strike?",
		"choice1":"EEE",
		"choice2":"QQW",
		"choice3":"WWQ",
		"choice4":"QWE",
		"correct":"EEE"
	},
	{
	"id":"83",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the effect of Orchid of Malevolence when used on an enemy hero?",
		"choice1":"Silence",
		"choice2":"Slow",
		"choice3":"Stun",
		"choice4":"Hex",
		"correct":"Silence"
	},
	{
	"id":"84",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the effect of Guinsoo's Scythe of Vice when used on an enemy?",
		"choice1":"Silence",
		"choice2":"Slow",
		"choice3":"Stun",
		"choice4":"Hex",
		"correct":"Hex"
	},
	{
	"id":"85",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the effect of Abyssal Blade when used on an enemy?",
		"choice1":"Silence",
		"choice2":"Slow",
		"choice3":"Stun",
		"choice4":"Hex",
		"correct":"Stun"
	},
	{
	"id":"86",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the effect of Rod of Atos when used on an enemy?",
		"choice1":"Silence",
		"choice2":"Cripple/Slow",
		"choice3":"Stun",
		"choice4":"Hex",
		"correct":"Cripple/Slow"
	},
	{
	"id":"87",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What is the name of Magina's ultimate?",
		"choice1":"Void",
		"choice2":"Mana Break",
		"choice3":"Blink",
		"choice4":"Mana Void",
		"correct":"Mana Void"
	},
	{
	"id":"88",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Who is the the Crystal Maiden?",
		"choice1":"Traxex",
		"choice2":"Rylai Crestfall",
		"choice3":"Ancient Apparition",
		"choice4":"Tuskarr",
		"correct":"Rylai Crestfall"
	},
	{
	"id":"89",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Who is the the Drow Ranger?",
		"choice1":"Traxex",
		"choice2":"Rylai Crestfall",
		"choice3":"Ancient Apparition",
		"choice4":"Tuskarr",
		"correct":"Traxex"
	},
	{
	"id":"90",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. What does the Dust of Appearance do?",
		"choice1":"Stun enemies within AOE",
		"choice2":"Reveals invisible enemy units within AOE",
		"choice3":"Slows enemy units within AOE ",
		"choice4":"Adds 9999 armour to allied units",
		"correct":"Reveals invisible enemy units within AOE"
	},
	{
	"id":"91",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Who has the ultimate Guardian Angel?",
		"choice1":"Omniknight",
		"choice2":"Chen",
		"choice3":"Lion",
		"choice4":"Sven",
		"correct":"Omniknight"
	},
	{
	"id":"92",
		"question":"In the game 'DotA'. Who is the Phantom Assassin?",
		"choice1":"Rikimaru",
		"choice2":"Lanaya",
		"choice3":"Mortred",
		"choice4":"Sven",
		"correct":"Mortred"
	},
	{
	"id":"93",
		"question":"In the Game 'Final Fantasy VII: Crisis Core', Who originally owns the Buster Sword?",
		"choice1":"Angeal",
		"choice2":"Sephiroth",
		"choice3":"Director Lazard",
		"choice4":"Genesis",
		"correct":"Angeal"
	},
	{
	"id":"94",
		"question":"In the Game 'Final Fantasy VII: Crisis Core', Who has the title 'Soldier Hero'?",
		"choice1":"Angeal",
		"choice2":"Sephiroth",
		"choice3":"Director Lazard",
		"choice4":"Genesis",
		"correct":"Sephiroth"
	},
	{
	"id":"95",
		"question":"Who is the main character in Final Fantasy XIII?",
		"choice1":"Cloud",
		"choice2":"Sephiroth",
		"choice3":"Squall",
		"choice4":"Lightning",
		"correct":"Lightning"
	},
	{
	"id":"96",
		"question":"Who is the main character in Final Fantasy VII:Crisis Core?",
		"choice1":"Squall",
		"choice2":"Sephiroth",
		"choice3":"Zack",
		"choice4":"Cloud",
		"correct":"Zack"
	},
	{
	"id":"96",
		"question":"Who gave Cloud Strife's Buster Sword?",
		"choice1":"Squall",
		"choice2":"Sephiroth",
		"choice3":"Zack",
		"choice4":"Cloud",
		"correct":"Zack"
	},
	{
	"id":"97",
		"question":"Whos face is used as the game icon of NBA 2k14?",
		"choice1":"LeBron James",
		"choice2":"Michael Jordan",
		"choice3":"Kevin Durant",
		"choice4":"Derrick Rose",
		"correct":"LeBron James"
	},
	{
	"id":"98",
		"question":"In the game Pokemon: Fire Red, who among these pokemon is not a Starter?",
		"choice1":"Charmander",
		"choice2":"Pikachu",
		"choice3":"Squirtle",
		"choice4":"Bulbasaur",
		"correct":"Pikachu"
	},
	{
	"id":"99",
		"question":"What kind of animal is Pikachu?",
		"choice1":"Cat",
		"choice2":"Dog",
		"choice3":"Mouse",
		"choice4":"Squirrel",
		"correct":"Mouse"
	}
		
	]

	
	
	
